[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "DT", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Did you notice anything to bring to the jury's attention today, that caused you that concern, that spidey sense that something's going wrong with what he's telling you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "notice", "anything", "to", "bring", "to", "the", "jury", "'s", "attention", "today", ",", "that", "caused", "you", "that", "concern", ",", "that", "spidey", "sense", "that", "something", "'s", "going", "wrong", "with", "what", "he", "'s", "telling", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Nothing I can articulate, no, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Nothing", "I", "can", "articulate", ",", "no", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Do you think given what happened today, Martin, that there's any likelihood George Zimmerman himself will give evidence now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "given", "what", "happened", "today", ",", "Martin", ",", "that", "there", "'s", "any", "likelihood", "George", "Zimmerman", "himself", "will", "give", "evidence", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WP", "VBN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I would say it'd be highly unlikely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "it", "'d", "be", "highly", "unlikely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "How much of that could be covered, and I stress could be, by the fact that they were criticized so widely for not taking, A, action in terms of charging Zimmerman on the night of this incident, in other words, basically, covering their own position?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "that", "could", "be", "covered", ",", "and", "I", "stress", "could", "be", ",", "by", "the", "fact", "that", "they", "were", "criticized", "so", "widely", "for", "not", "taking", ",", "A", ",", "action", "in", "terms", "of", "charging", "Zimmerman", "on", "the", "night", "of", "this", "incident", ",", "in", "other", "words", ",", "basically", ",", "covering", "their", "own", "position", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", ",", "DT", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, I mean, it's a legitimate question to ask.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "legitimate", "question", "to", "ask", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJS", ":", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "DT", ":", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Why would he feign total lack of knowledge when there's just three street names?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "he", "feign", "total", "lack", "of", "knowledge", "when", "there", "'s", "just", "three", "street", "names", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, I think that's very telling because the biggest -- the biggest I think piece of evidence against George Zimmerman is his own words to the -- to the nonemergency officer, where he said that Trayvon -- he goes oh, S, he's running, and he gets out of his car.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "very", "telling", "because", "the", "biggest", "--", "the", "biggest", "I", "think", "piece", "of", "evidence", "against", "George", "Zimmerman", "is", "his", "own", "words", "to", "the", "--", "to", "the", "nonemergency", "officer", ",", "where", "he", "said", "that", "Trayvon", "--", "he", "goes", "oh", ",", "S", ",", "he", "'s", "running", ",", "and", "he", "gets", "out", "of", "his", "car", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "What did you make of it in totality?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "it", "in", "totality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, in totality, Piers, you know, I was on your show just the other day, and I was telling you how it looked like.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "totality", ",", "Piers", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "was", "on", "your", "show", "just", "the", "other", "day", ",", "and", "I", "was", "telling", "you", "how", "it", "looked", "like", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "The fact that George Zimmerman said to you, thank god, I hope somebody did videotape the event or the whole event, what -- his statement, what did that indicate to you?", "question_tokens": ["The", "fact", "that", "George", "Zimmerman", "said", "to", "you", ",", "thank", "god", ",", "I", "hope", "somebody", "did", "videotape", "the", "event", "or", "the", "whole", "event", ",", "what", "--", "his", "statement", ",", "what", "did", "that", "indicate", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Either he was telling the truth or he was a complete pathological liar.", "answer_tokens": ["Either", "he", "was", "telling", "the", "truth", "or", "he", "was", "a", "complete", "pathological", "liar", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "You think he was telling the truth?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "he", "was", "telling", "the", "truth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "In other words, this is really corroborating their own positions?", "question_tokens": ["In", "other", "words", ",", "this", "is", "really", "corroborating", "their", "own", "positions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "That -- obviously not the least bit naive.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "--", "obviously", "not", "the", "least", "bit", "naive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "CD", "RBR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Very -- yes?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "--", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "There is one more thing.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "one", "more", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Do you think that she will be called back at this stage?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "she", "will", "be", "called", "back", "at", "this", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rachel"], "LOCATION": ["Sanford"]}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Particularly the charge, I guess, that lays itself at your door that she was somehow underprepared or underrehearsed?", "question_tokens": ["Particularly", "the", "charge", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "that", "lays", "itself", "at", "your", "door", "that", "she", "was", "somehow", "underprepared", "or", "underrehearsed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Well, as you know, Piers, you and I spoke, and I became Rachel's lawyer last week, and that was by request of some individuals that attend church with her, that are former law enforcement officers that believed that she was not really prepared to go to Sanford and testify in the case, that she had absolutely no clue as to what was getting ready to take place.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "you", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "you", "and", "I", "spoke", ",", "and", "I", "became", "Rachel", "'s", "lawyer", "last", "week", ",", "and", "that", "was", "by", "request", "of", "some", "individuals", "that", "attend", "church", "with", "her", ",", "that", "are", "former", "law", "enforcement", "officers", "that", "believed", "that", "she", "was", "not", "really", "prepared", "to", "go", "to", "Sanford", "and", "testify", "in", "the", "case", ",", "that", "she", "had", "absolutely", "no", "clue", "as", "to", "what", "was", "getting", "ready", "to", "take", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "When you heard her say that, did you think that was a mistake, that it was obviously a racist comment or a very offensive comment?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "heard", "her", "say", "that", ",", "did", "you", "think", "that", "was", "a", "mistake", ",", "that", "it", "was", "obviously", "a", "racist", "comment", "or", "a", "very", "offensive", "comment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Well, unfortunately, that is the vernacular of young teenagers these days.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "unfortunately", ",", "that", "is", "the", "vernacular", "of", "young", "teenagers", "these", "days", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "How did you think his testimony went down today?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "think", "his", "testimony", "went", "down", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Well, Chris is a straight shooter.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Chris", "is", "a", "straight", "shooter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "And because they both come out today and give extensive testimony, saying, yes, we found him very credible, and consistent and so on, that lends sucker to why they didn't do anything?", "question_tokens": ["And", "because", "they", "both", "come", "out", "today", "and", "give", "extensive", "testimony", ",", "saying", ",", "yes", ",", "we", "found", "him", "very", "credible", ",", "and", "consistent", "and", "so", "on", ",", "that", "lends", "sucker", "to", "why", "they", "did", "n't", "do", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I would disagree because if you look at the situation, they're not the ones that make the charging decision.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "disagree", "because", "if", "you", "look", "at", "the", "situation", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "the", "ones", "that", "make", "the", "charging", "decision", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Do you know yet what happened here to cause such a calamitous loss of life?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "yet", "what", "happened", "here", "to", "cause", "such", "a", "calamitous", "loss", "of", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Well, don't really actually know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "do", "n't", "really", "actually", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "In all your time as a governor, have you had to deal with anything that's hit you quite as hard as this in the state?", "question_tokens": ["In", "all", "your", "time", "as", "a", "governor", ",", "have", "you", "had", "to", "deal", "with", "anything", "that", "'s", "hit", "you", "quite", "as", "hard", "as", "this", "in", "the", "state", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "No, I don't believe so.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "believe", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "And these firemen, these Hotshots, to lose so many in one incident like this, a terrible blow for you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "these", "firemen", ",", "these", "Hotshots", ",", "to", "lose", "so", "many", "in", "one", "incident", "like", "this", ",", "a", "terrible", "blow", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Yes, it's an absolutely horrible situation, a tragic for all of us.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "an", "absolutely", "horrible", "situation", ",", "a", "tragic", "for", "all", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "In terms of the investigation into what happened, do you have any more insight into how they found themselves in such an awful situation?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "the", "investigation", "into", "what", "happened", ",", "do", "you", "have", "any", "more", "insight", "into", "how", "they", "found", "themselves", "in", "such", "an", "awful", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "No, at this point the fire is still under investigation.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "at", "this", "point", "the", "fire", "is", "still", "under", "investigation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Yarnell"], "LOCATION": ["Prescott"]}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Is that making it a lot worse than a fire like this normally would be at this time of year?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "making", "it", "a", "lot", "worse", "than", "a", "fire", "like", "this", "normally", "would", "be", "at", "this", "time", "of", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Yes, the temperatures actually in Prescott are reaching 102 degrees down in the valley where Yarnell is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "the", "temperatures", "actually", "in", "Prescott", "are", "reaching", "102", "degrees", "down", "in", "the", "valley", "where", "Yarnell", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Tell me about him, what kind of man was he?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "him", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "man", "was", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "He was the best kind.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "the", "best", "kind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Do you have any inkling yourself as to how so many of them have lost their lives in this situation?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "inkling", "yourself", "as", "to", "how", "so", "many", "of", "them", "have", "lost", "their", "lives", "in", "this", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "WRB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "That's not something that I could really comment on.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "something", "that", "I", "could", "really", "comment", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: How are you feeling, Nik?", "question_tokens": ["NIDENTIFIED", "MALE", ":", "How", "are", "you", "feeling", ",", "Nik", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Good.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard about this poor woman and her death?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "heard", "about", "this", "poor", "woman", "and", "her", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Well, of course, deeply saddened and my condolences go out to her and her entire family, as well as the Cirque du Soleil family.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", ",", "deeply", "saddened", "and", "my", "condolences", "go", "out", "to", "her", "and", "her", "entire", "family", ",", "as", "well", "as", "the", "Cirque", "du", "Soleil", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130701pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "You were just one trip away, aren't you, from calamity?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "just", "one", "trip", "away", ",", "are", "n't", "you", ",", "from", "calamity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "It's -- it is true.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "it", "is", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]